Guide to the Bruce Baillie papers M1913
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Film Notes
  - "Quick Billy" production notes: 3 of 5, ca. 1970. (Oversize-box 34, Folder 9)
  - "Quick Billy" production notes: 4 of 5, ca. 1970. (Oversize-box 34, Folder 10)
  - "Quick Billy" production notes: 5 of 5, ca. 1970. (Oversize-box 34, Folder 11)
  - Travel Tour, 1977. (Oversize-box 34, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Booklets, 1955-2010. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Film Magazines and Papers, 1960s. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Film Publications, 1960s. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Canyon Cinema show posters, 1960-1970s. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Film Notes, 1960s-1970s. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Film Correspondence, 1961-1966. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Canyon Cinema Correspondence, 1962-1964. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Film Correspondence, 1963-1964. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Film posters, reviews, and announcements, 1960s (1 of 5). (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Film posters, reviews, and announcements, 1960s (2 of 5). (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Film posters, reviews, and announcements, 1960s (3 of 5)., box (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Film posters, reviews, and announcements, 1960s (4 of 5). (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Film posters, reviews, and announcements, 1960s (5 of 5). (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Pacifica Radio, 1964. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Canyon Cinema Papers, 1964-1974. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Canyon Cinema Papers, 1965. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Film Correspondence, 1965. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Film Correspondence, 1966-1967 (1 of 3). (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Film Correspondence, 1966-1967 (2 of 3). (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Film Correspondence, 1966-1967 (3 of 3). (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - "Castro Street" notebooks, 1966. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Film Festival materials, 1967-2005. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Print Sales, 1968. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Bell and Howell Productions papers, 1968. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1968. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Summer School, 1968. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Film Correspondence, 1968-1969. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Anthology Film Archives, 1968-1969. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Robert Flaherty Seminar, 1969. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Festivals, 1969. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Receipts, 1969. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Film Correspondence, 1970. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - New York papers, 1970s. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Filmography, 1970s. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Film Files, 1970s-1980s. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Film Notes, 1975. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Print Sales Correspondence, 1975. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Notes and Papers, 1980s. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Film notes, 1980s-1990s. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "Dr. Bish" news and periodicals, 1980. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative des cineastes independants catalog, 1980. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Essays and Publications, 1980s. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Advertisement Papers, 1980-1981. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Film Notes, 1980s-2000s. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1981-2007. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Scott Nygren "Mythic Vision" SUNY Buffalo Ph.D. Dissertation, 1982. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Talks with Kathleen, 1982-1988. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Advertisement Papers, 1984. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Japan Trip, 1984-1985. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - The Bakery Show Japan, 1985. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Film-making co-ops papers, 1985-1990. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Video Notes, 1987-1988. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1987-2010. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - "P-38" Notes, 1989-1990. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - "P-38" Review, 1990. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "P-38" poem and related papers, 1990. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Film Papers, 1990. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Canyon Cinema News, 1990s. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Film Notes, 1990s-2000s (1 of 3). (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Film Notes, 1990s-2000s (2 of 3). (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Film Notes, 1990s-2000s (3 of 3). (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - "Release Print" newsletter, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - "Light Struck" newsletters, 1991-1992. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - "Anthology Film Archives" issues, 1991-2008. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Newsletters, 1991-2008. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Studio Table Notes, 1992. (Flat-box 72, Folder 1)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1992-1994. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - "The Golden God" script, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Film Papers, 1994. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Film and Video general business, 1994 (1 of 2). (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Film and Video general business (2 of 2). (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "A Celtic Journey" academic paper, 1994. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Kathleen Connor Ph.D. Dissertation, 1994. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1995-2005 (1 of 3). (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1995-2005 (2 of 3). (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Studio Table Misc., 1995-2005 (3 of 3). (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - "Chapter XI", 1995-2006. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - "Chapter X", 1996. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - "Chapter XI", 1997 (1 of 2). (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - "Chapter XI", 1997 (2 of 2). (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - "Chapter X" notes, 1997. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - "Chapter XI", 1998 (1 of 2). (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - "Chapter XI", 1998 (2 of 2). (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Film Correspondence, 1998-1999. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Film Business Correspondence, 1998-2005. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - "Chapter XI", 2000-2007. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Baillie Website Content, 2000. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Film Papers, 2001-2006. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - "Chapter XI", 2002-2003. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Monaco Lab, 2007. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Table Studio Misc., 2007-2011. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - "Heaven" Athens Biennale book, 2009. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Table Studio Misc., 2011. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - "Chapter XI" notes, 2012. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - New American Cinema papers, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Film Awards and Festival Materials, 1964-1973. (Oversize-box 71, Folder 2)
  - Film Posters, 2001. (Oversize-box 71, Folder 3)
  - Film Notes, n.d. (Oversize-box 71, Folder 4)
  - Film posters (Map-folder 73)
- Series 4: Professorial Work
  - Bard College Course Outlines, 1974-1975. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Bard College Student Papers, 1974-1975. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bard College Baillie Evaluation, 1975. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bard Commencement, 1975. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Bard College Baillie Resignation Letter, 1975. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bard College Publication: "Let there be light", ca. 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bard College Notes, 1976-1977. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Bard College Observer, 1976-1977. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Bard College Speech, 1977. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Bard College Observer, 1977-1995. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Film Course Papers, 1979. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Evergreen State Student Exams, 1981. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - TESC Grant/Residency Papers, 1981. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Evergreen State and Misc. University Correspondence, 1981-1983. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Evergreen State Papers, 1982. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Evergreen Flyers, 1982. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Evergreen College Papers, 1982. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Evergreen State College papers, 1982. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Poetry and Evergreen State Correspondence, ca. 1983. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Evergreen State Student Papers, ca. 1983. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Evergreen State Papers and Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Evergreen College Notes, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Rice University Papers, 1952-1970. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Donna Bloomer Papers, 1969-1971. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Bard College Correspondence, 1970s (1 of 3). (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Bard College Correspondence, 1970s (2 of 3). (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Bard College Correspondence, 1970s (3 of 3). (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Bard College Papers, 1974-1975. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Bard College Oberserver, 1976. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Evergreen State College photographs and notes, 1981. (Box 70, Folder 8)